<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Old Delhi Tourism</string>
    <string name="authur">Shikher Gupta</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate App</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>

    <string name="history">Delhi, capital of independent India is famous for its beauty, culture, tradition, dynamism and effervescent history. Delhi is perfect blend of old and new, modern and traditional. \nOld Delhi is known for its monuments, complicated streets, social customs, old bazaars, rich variety of food and traditional lifestyle where as New Delhi is completely different in architecture, lifestyle and have well planned roads. Diverse cultural elements and variegated lifestyle absorbed into the daily life of this wonderful city have enriched its character and made it one of the most favored tourist attractions in India.\n \n \nHistory of Delhi enumerates a saga of various dynasties and empires which have left behind a plethora of amazing monuments that the grandeur and glory of bygone ages. Delhi has played an important role in Indian history.\nThere have been at least eight cities around modern Delhi. The first four cities were to the south part of the state where the Qutab Minar stands. Delhi was called Indraprastha in the earliest times and that city was near present-day Purana Qila. At the beginning of the 12th century, Delhi was ruled by the last Hindu kingdom of Tomara and Chauhan dynasties. The empire of those Hindu rulers was near Qutab Minar and Suraj Kund. This city was followed by Siri, which was constructed by Ala-ud-din. In the 12th century, Siri was built near present day Hauz Khas. The third Delhi was Tughlaqabad, which stood 10 km south-east of the Qutub Minar. The fourth Delhi was also built by Tughlaqs that dates from the 14th century. Known as Jahanpanah, it also stood near the Qutur Minar.\n\nShah Jahan shifted his capital from Agra and announced Delhi, Shahjahanabad as his new capital. Shahjahanabad is largely preserved and corresponds to present day Old Delhi. Finally, the eighth Delhi, New Delhi, was constructed by the Britishers- they move their capital from Calcutta to Delhi and announced in 1911 but construction was not completed and the city officially inaugurated in 1931. </string>

    <string name="starting_text_1">\n\n\n\nWelcome To Old Delhi Tourism</string>

    <string name="starting_text_2">Select Options From the Left to Know More</string>

    <string name="red_fort">Delhi\'s most famous monument, the Red Fort, stands as a powerful reminder of the Mughal emperors who ruled India. \nIts walls, which stretch for over two kilometers (1.2 miles), were built in 1638 to keep out invaders. However, they failed to stop the fort being captured by the Sikhs and the British. \n\nTo take your imagination back to the ancient era, a one hour sound and light show of the fort\'s history is held each evening.\n\nLocation: Opposite Chandni Chowk, Old Delhi.\nEntry Cost: $5 or 250 rupees. Free for children under 15 years.\nOpening Hours: Sunrise until sunset. Closed Mondays.</string>

    <string name="chandni_chowk">Chandni Chowk, the main street of old Delhi, is a shocking contrast to the wide, orderly streets of New Delhi. \nCars, cycle rickshaws, hand-pulled carts, pedestrians, and animals all compete for space. It\'s chaotic, crumbling and congested, but completely captivating as well. \n\nAs one of the oldest and busiest markets in India, its narrow winding lanes are full of inexpensive jewelry, fabrics, and electronics.\n\n For the more adventurous, Chandni Chowk is an excellent place to come to sample some of Delhi\'s street food. The renowned Karim Hotel, a Delhi dining institution, is also located there.\n\nLocation: Old Delhi, near the Red Fort and Jama Masjid.</string>

    <string name="bus">For foreigners, it’s easiest to make ticket bookings at the International Tourist Bureau (23405156; 1st Flour, New Delhi train station; 8am-8pm Mon-Sat, to 2pm Sun). \n\nDo not believe anyone who tells you it has shifted, closed or burnt down – this is a rampant scam to divert you elsewhere. There are reportedly railway porters involved in scams, so stay on your toes and don’t let anyone stop you from going to the 1st floor of the main building for bookings. \n\nWhen making reservations at the International Tourist Bureau, tickets must be paid for in rupees backed up by money-exchange certificates (or ATM receipts) or in US dollars, euros or pounds sterling; any change is given in rupees. Bring your passport. There’s a train booking counter at the airport.</string>

    <string name="air">The most convenient Indian Airlines office (23313317; F-Block, Malhotra Bldg, Connaught Place; 10am-1pm and 2-5pm Mon-Sat) is at Connaught Place. \nThere\’s also a ticket office at Safdarjang airfield (24631337; Aurobindo Marg; 7am-11pm). For Indian Airlines\’ recorded flight arrival and departure details, dial 1407.\n\nOther domestic airlines\n\nAir Deccan (no office; inquiries 9818177008)\nJagson Airlines (23721593; Vandana Bldg, 11 Tolstoy Marg; 9.30am-6pm Mon-Sat)\nJet Airways (39841111; 40 N-Block, Connaught Place; 9am-9pm Mon-Fri, to 6pm Sat and Sun)\nKingfisher Airlines (23730238; 42 N-Block, Connaught Place; 8am-9pm Mon-Fri, 10am-6pm Sat and Sun)\nSahara Airlines (23326851; Gopal Das Bhavan, 28 Barakhamba Rd, Connaught Place; 10am-5pm Mon-Fri, 9am-4pm Sat)\n</string>
</resources>
